# **Tanya Therese Bryhn Romano**

Adresse: Doktor Wendts Gate 4,

Phone: 45494996 • E-Mail: tanyabryhnromano@gmail.com / post@wowbrow.no, Født: 01.02.1987

### **Profil**

I am a positive and approachable women from Norway with good experience in marketing and branding. I find myself outgoing, creative and independent. I communicate well with people and love being social. I have always had an entrepreneur in me and love building up a corporation from nothing to success. In Norway I have my own two companies running a beauty concept consisting of my own beauty salon. As I am also one of Norways best microblading technicians and therefore I travel all around Norway and arrange training courses. From this I have developed my own product line and my very own webshop. As WOWBROW became a success, I now have 6 employees



in Norway. From this we just started a mother branch in our company with does import of beauty treatment machine called Skinlift 360.

Last year our revenue in WOWBROW was 2.2 million NOK with only 2 employees. And we know this year that it will double.

Our new company is operating with much higher rates and we have an estimated revenue of 36. Million nok. Main purpose of the company is being a machine supplier, selling each machine for 30.000 nok eks VAT. Estimated sale per month is 100 machines. This is the reason for me applying for entrepreneur visa in Canada as I wish to open both WOWBROW and Skinlift 360 in your region. I already have good connections and people waiting for me to start the business cooperation with them. All on them are quite successful already today.

I do have abroad work experience with I believe is the reason for me being successful today. It has been an amazing journey and a learning curve I could be without.

I am also a mother of a lovely 2 year old boy which means the world to me.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## WOWBROW (august 2016 - ) (Oslo)

CEO

Owner and founder of Norways biggest Brow Concept WOWBROW, which provides beauty treatments, training courses and have a own product line and webshop. www.wowbrow.no.

## Four Seasons Spa (September - Desember 2016)(Oslo, Aker Brygge)

Head of Operations

Head of daily operations, and in charge of 6 employees in Norways finest Spa. Also offering WOWBROW's services in this Spa.

## Travel Retail Norway (August 2015- Juni 2016) (Gardemoen)

Retail Consultant

## United Influencers (2015-dd) (Bryggegata 9, Oslo)

Media Influencer

### Norsk Ballett Institutt (2003- 2015)

Pedagogical teacher(Oslo & Akershus)

## Professional Ballet Dancer (2009-2013) (Oslo, Norway)

Freelance dancer.

Worked as a professional dancer after my education at the National Academy of the Arts. Danced in big productions such as a Tribute to Michael Jackson, TV shows, Eurovison and Danced for famous Scandinavian artists as: Eric Saade, Datarock & Loreen to name a few. Worked with famous choreographs as a Toni Ferraz, Tine Aspaas, Lise Tiller & Thomas Glans.

### Solid Publications (Oct 2011 - Jan 2012) (Oslo)

Media consultant

# **Tanya Bryhn Romano**

Page 3

## Drøbak Danseklubb (Jul 2011 - Jun 2013) (Drøbak)

Owner and Founder

Owner of a dancing school in Drøbak, Norway.

## Club Mango (April 2010 - May 2011) (Oslo)

Event Manager

## Grim (Okt 2009 - Mars 2010) (Oslo)

Ass. Manager

Assisting Manager in one of Norways biggest Urban clothing line.

## Heer Skole (Aug - Sept 2009) (Drøbak)

Pedagogical assistant

Pedagogical assistant at Primary school of Heer.

## **Stavanger Kommune (Mars - Juni 2008) (Stavanger)**

Homecare

Assisting older and sick people.

## Neste Stopp og Kremmerhuset (Aug 2003- May 2007) (Ski & Stavanger)

Retail consultant

## Drøbak Golf Café, (April - Aug 2004) (Drøbak)

Waiter

## Galleri Cafe Teskje (Jul 2001- Mai 2003) (Drøbak)

Waiter

#### **Attended Courses**

- How to become a great influencer w/ Thomas Moen (named as the 30'st powerful man in Media-Norway)
- The Future of Media
- Google Analytics m/ Thomas Moen
- Talentprogram i sosiale medier m/ United Influencers
- Microblading Advanced kurs, Irina Chen
- Masterclass Rebecka Chung, Shading techniques
- Masterclass Rebecka Chung, Lipliner techniques
- Masterclass Rebecka Chung, Eyeliner techniques
- HMS Course in Health and Safety regulations

### **OTHER QUALITIES**

- Over average good in marketing which was my main field in business school and why my company reached success.
- Speak fluently English
- Speak little Spanish
- Speak fluently Swedish & Danish
- I have good experience in staff management and team building.
- Knowledge good in graphic design. Know how to use, Adobe Illustrator, photoshop, Final Cut and Lightroom.
- Knowledge very good in Microsoft Word & Excel.
- Knowledge very good in sosiale medier
- Knowledge very good Google Analytics.
- Knowledge very good in facebook for business.
- I am also good in coding websites, especially Wordpress.

## **EDUCATION**

# BI Handelshøyskolen i Oslo (2014-2015)

Business Economy
1 year study

# National Academy of the Arts (2009-2011)

Bachelor program Jazzdans
(I went here 2 of 3 years, and had to quit because if injuries)
(120 study points)

## **Universitetet i Stavanger (2006-2008)**

Dans og Pedagogikk 2 years (120 study points)

**Bagamoyo Collage of Art**, (exchange student in Tanzania) jan-mars 2008 The Noda-prosjectet.

# Ski Videregående Skole - (2003-2006)

Danselinjen

Alværn Ungdomskole - High school (2000-2003)

Heer Barneskole - Primary School (1994-2000)

# **REFERANCES:**

## www.wowbrow.no

Instagram: wowbrowmicrobladin

Facebook: wowbrownorge

Faceboo: skinlift360 Nordic & skinlift360

David Chen 98 88 88 83 (Eier, Four Seasons Spa)

Julie Holst 92 85 58 81 (CEO i United Influencers Norge)

Marco Bicanic 97 86 86 77 (Brassmedia.no)

Kjerstin Kartrud (Norsk Ballett Institutt)

Winnie Galvan 64 93 28 90 (Galleri Cafe Teskje)

Jamina Iversen: 90 63 91 75 (Grim)

Huyen Hueng: 95 93 23 09 (Circle Dansestudio)

Kristine Bjørneset Flø: 41 26 40 96 (Neste Stopp)